Rizki Pratama

Bandar Lampung, Lampung, Indonesia

eyefins7896@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/scotter96

Summary

Hi, top of the morning to you!

I'm Rizki Pratama, you could call me Tama, I'm a Software Engineer with 7+ years worth of experiences in Computer Software and Game Development industry. Uses Odoo with Python daily, and Unity with C# on the side.

Experience



Odoo Developer

CrediBook (YC W22)

Jul 2022 - Present (6 months +)

Software Developer

Freelance

Jun 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

- Reviewed project specifications and designed technology solutions that met or exceeded performance expectations.
- Offered experience with Python and SQL.
- Worked on 17 Apps for Android.
- Worked on 30+ modules with 2 major modules on Odoo (OpenERP).
- Multimedia based projects: Augmented Reality (AR) & Virtual Reality (VR).
- Structured workflow to keep track of the tasks & milestones.

Odoo Developer

PT Tunas Dwipa Matra

Jun 2019 - Jul 2022 (3 years 2 months)

- Resolved product design, acquisition and launch concerns to achieve customer's targeted business goals.
- · Communicated technical development stages and provided design support to stakeholders.
- Participated in design and planning exercises for future software rollouts.
- Participated with clients in discussion meetings.
- Maximized proficiency in Odoo and Python to prepare and present technical reports and effectively support cross-functional teams.
- Mentored 3 new employees to bring them up to speed on projects, resulting in quicker overall completion milestones.
- Key contributor in the design and implementation of new features for company's internal ERP system.
- · Resolved product issue through consumer testing.

Game Developer

Fun Technologies Studio

Aug 2015 - Jul 2021 (6 years)

- Worked on 8 games, along with my own games that I published on Android via Google Play or other services.
- Structured workflow to keep track of the tasks & milestones.
- Experiences in both 2D & 3D perspectives.

Laboratory Assistant

IBI Darmajaya

Sep 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 9 months)

I am a member of the team that makes sure the Laboratory's electrical components and computers being used for Lectures in this campus works accordingly.

Freelance Writer

Freelance

Nov 2015 - Jun 2017 (1 year 8 months)

Worked on 10+ projects using Office application (Office Word and Office Excel)

Education

IBI Darmajaya

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science 2014 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications

TOEFL (Test Of English as a Foreign Language) - IIB Darmajaya Issued May 2018 - Expires May 2019

0063-DLC-TOEFL-0501-2018

FCNS (Foresec Certified in Networking Security) - PT LIFELONG LEARNING 0918-014966

Skills

C++ • Adobe Photoshop • Android • Robotic Process Automation (RPA) • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML • Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) • REST APIs • Game Development

Honors & Awards

3rd place Computer Olympiad (District level) - Tim Olimpiade Sains Nasional

Indonesia

Mar 2013

Best Graduate of the Faculty of Computer Systems in Year 2018 Even Period -

IBI Darmajaya

Nov 2018

I graduated with GPA 3.73 out of 4